Contact

Gakhar Apartments, Faizabad, Rawalpindi (+92) 3129567424 (Mobile) ghulam.ali282@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ghulam-aliqureshi (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

.NET Framework

C#

AngularJS

Languages

English

Urdu

Certifications

Primavera P6 Essential Training

Ghulam Ali

Software Developer II at S&P Global Islamabad

Summary

Self-driven Full Stack Developer with 3 years of experience in applications development. Having in-depth knowledge of OOD and Design Patterns with ability to understand and transform complex business requirements into software, ensuring applications are delivered on time, to specification, are scale-able, performance optimized and maintainable.

Experience

S&P Global Software Developer II July 2021 - Present (9 months) Islāmābād, Pakistan

e-strats Software Engineer June 2020 - July 2021 (1 year 2 months) Islāmābād, Pakistan

TingbA Technologies Software Developer February 2018 - April 2020 (2 years 3 months) Islamabad

Education

University of Azad Jammu and Kashmir BSCS, Computer Science · (2009 - 2013)